Guide to the Samuel P. Hays Post-World War II Radical Movements Publications Collection, 1915-1982 AIS.1981.18
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Religious Periodicals, 1946-1982; I.
  - Presbyterian Guardian (Philadelphia, PA: Presbyterian Publishing Corp.), v. 35 no. 5-10, 1966; v. 36-38, 1967-1969; v. 39 no. 1-2, 1970, 13.
  - Presbyterian Key (Philadelphia, PA), v. 25 no. 2, Summer 1968, 14.
  - Presbyterian Journal (Waterville, NC: Southern Presbyterian Journal Co.), v. 24 no. 50-52, 1966; v. 25-30, 1967-1972, 1. (Box 17)
  - Presbyterian Layman (Philadelphia, PA), v. 1-5, 1968-Jan. 1973; v. 6, Feb. 1973-Jan. 1974; v. 7, 1974/1975; v. 8-10, 1975-1977; v. 11, 1978 (lacks Oct./Nov.); v. 12, 1979/1980 (lacks May 1979); v. 13, 1980; v. 14, Jan.-May 1981; v. 15 no. 1-2, Jan./Feb.-March/April 1982, 1. (Box 18)
  - Profile of the National Association of Evangelicals (Wheaton, IL), v. 2, no. 1-2, Jan.-Feb. 1969, 2.
  - Progressive Calvinism (South Holland, IL), v. 3 no. 12, Dec. 1957, 3.
  - Prophetic Herald (Spokane, WA), v. 27 no. 7, 9, July, Sept. 1966; v. 28 no. 1-12, 1967; v. 29, no. 1-12, 1968; v. 30 no. 1-12, 1969; v. 31 no. 1-12, 1970; v. 32 no. 1-8, Jan.-Aug. 1971, 4.
  - Prophetic Newsletter (Colton, CA: World Prophetic Ministry), Oct., Dec. 1966; 1967-1968; Jan. 1969; March 1970; Dec. 1971, 5.
  - Prophetic Reporter (Tulsa, OK), no. 3, 1971; Summer 1981, 6.
  - Quaker Life (Richmond, IN), v. 6 no. 12, Dec. 1965; v. 7-9, 1966-1968; v. 10, 1969 (lacks March-April); v. 11-12, 1970-1971; v. 13, Jan.-March 1972, 7.
  - Quaker Theological Newsnotes (Martinsville, NJ), v. 9 no. 1, June 1966, 8.
  - Railroad Evangelist (Indianapolis, IN), v. 31 no. 6-7, May-June 1970, 1. (Box 19)
  - Reality: a National Monthly of Christian Belief and Opinion (Minneapolis, MN), v. 2 no. 9, 11-12, Sept., Nov.-Dec. 1966; v. 3 no. 1-4, Jan.-July 1967, 2.
  - Reformed Presbyterian Reporter (Walker, IA), v. 100, Feb., May-Dec. 1966; v. 101, Jan.-Oct. 1967; v. 102, Nov.1967-Jan. 1969, 3.
  - Religion and Race Newsletter (Pittsburgh, PA: Pittsburgh Area Religion and Race Council), 1 issue, unnumbered and undated, 4.
  - Remnant (St. Paul, MN), v. 1, 1967; v. 2, 1968; v. 3 no. 1-6, Jan.-March 1970; Suppl., Oct. 31, 1971, 5.
  - Restorer (New York, NY: Presbyterian Lay Committee), v. 1 no. 1-6, 8-9, 1967, 6.
  - Revelator (Laguna Beach, CA: The Little Church by the Sea, Inc.), v. 10, no. 1-2, June-July 1966, 7.
  - Ruff Times (Alamo, CA), 9 issues, 1979-1981, 8.
  - Schoolhouse Weathervane: A Christian Analysis (Wheaton, IL: National Association of Christian Schools), v. 1 no. 1-3, Oct. 1967-March 1968, 9.
  - Signs of the Times (Mountain View, CA), v. 93, no. 8-9, 12, Aug.-Sept., Dec., 1966; v. 94, no. 1-8, Jan.-Aug., 1967, 10.
  - Social Progress (Crawfordsville, IN: United Presbyterian Church), July/Aug. 1966, 11.
  - Sola Scriptura (Studio City, CA), v. 1 no. 1, July/Aug. 1970, 12.
  - Soul Patrol (Philadelphia, PA), v. 4 no. 4, Aug./Sept 1975; v. 5 no. 5, Nov./Dec. 1975, 13.
  - Sounds of Truth and Tradition (New York, NY: Catholic Traditionalist Movement), Fall 1969; Spring, Fall 1970; Summer 1971, 14.
  - Southern Methodist (Orangeburg, SC: Southern Methodist Church), v. 24 no. 3-12, March-Dec. 1966; v. 25-27, 1967-1969; v. 28 no. 1-4, Jan.-April 1970, 15.
  - Special Alert (Merrimac, MA), no. 19-28, May 1981-April 1982, 16.
  - Standard (Chicago, IL: Baptist General Conference), v. 56 no. 5-26, Feb. 28-Dec. 19, 1966; v. 57-59, 1967-1969, 17.
  - Standard (Chicago, IL: Baptist General Conference), v. 60 no. 1-9, Jan.-May 4, 1970, 1. (Box 20)
  - Star of Zion (Charlotte, NC: African Methodist Episcopal Zion Church), v. 91 no. 24-50, Jan.-Dec. 1968; v. 92-96, 1969-1973; v. 97 no. 1-17, Jan.-Aug., 1974, 2.
  - Sunday School Times and Gospel Herald (Cleveland, OH), v. 64 no. 17, Sept. 1, 1968, 3.
  - Showers of Blessing (Denver, CO: House of Prayer for All People), 547-661, July 1966-Jan. 1976; 663-735, March 1976-March 1982, 1. (Box 21)
  - Sword of the Lord (Murfreesboro, TN), v. 32 no. 30, 42-52, July-Dec. 1966; v. 33-37, 1967-1971, 1. (Box 22)
  - Sword of the Lord (Murfreesboro, TN), v. 38-39, 1972-1973; v. 42 no. 28-53, 1976; v. 43 no. 1-13, 1977, 1. (Box 23)
  - TVD: The Voice of Deliverance (Dallas, TX), v. 7 no. 2, 4, March/April, July/Aug. 1973;v. 9 no. 1, 3-4, Jan./Feb., May/June-Sept./Oct. 1974; v. 10 no. 1-5, Jan./Feb.-Sept./Oct. 1975; v. 11 no. 1-6, Jan./Feb-Nov./Dec. 1976; v. 12 no.1-2, 5-6, Jan./Feb.-March/April, Sept./Oct.-Nov./Dec. 1977; v. 13 no. 1, 3, Jan./Feb, May/June 1978; v. 14 no. 2, March/April 1979; v. 15, no.1, 3, 5, Feb., April/May, July/Aug. 1980, 2.
  - These Times (Nashville, TN: Southern Publishing Association), Oct.-Dec. 1976; 1977-1981; Jan.-March 1982, 3.
  - Through to Victory (Ridgecrest, CA), v. 6 no. 2-11, 1966; v. 7 no. 1-11, 1967, 4.
  - Together (Nashville, TN: The Methodist Publishing House), v. 12 no. 7- v. 13 no. 2, July 1968-Feb. 1969, 5.
  - Torch (Bass, AR), v. 7 no. 1-6, March-Sept./Oct. 1975; v. 8 no. 1, March 1976, 6.
  - Triumph (Washington, DC), v. 1 no. 1-4, 1966; v. 2-8, 1967-1973, 1. (Box 24)
  - Truth and Liberty Magazine (Hopkins, MN), Feb., April, July-Sept., Nov., 1965; Feb.-Sept., Nov.-Dec., 1966; 1967-1968; Jan.-May, July-Dec., 1969; 1970; Jan.-Nov., 1971, 2.
  - Twin Circle: Classics Illustrated, no. 2, 4, 10, 16, 48, 68, 128, 535, 1967-1968, 3.
  - Una Voce in the U.S. Newsletter (New York, NY), no. 7, March 1, 1969; no. 11-14, Nov. 15, 1969-May 1, 1970; no. 16-17, Sept. 25, 1970-Jan. 15, 1971; no. 20-23, July 10-Nov. 15, 1971; no. 25, March 17, 1972, 4.
  - Una Voce in the U.S. Open Letter (New York, NY), Sept. 12, 1969; Dec. 1, 1969; April 15, 1970; April 29, 1970, 5.
  - United Evangelical Action (Wheaton, IL: National Association of Evangelicals), v. 25-26, March 1966-Feb. 1968; v. 27 no. 1-2, March-Spring 1968, 6.
  - Universal Challenger (Finleyville, PA: The Voice of the Nazarene), v. 5 no. 10-12, May-Sept. 1966; v. 6, Oct. 1966-Nov. 1967; v. 7 no. 1-6, Dec. 1967-June 1968; v. 8 no. 2, 11, Oct. 1968, Aug. 1969, 7.
  - Twin Circle: the National Catholic Press (Los Angeles, CA: Twin Circle Pub. Co.), v. 1-4, 1967-1970; v. 5, no. 6-8,19, Feb. 7-21, May 9, 1971; v. 6, no. 41, Oct. 13, 1972, 1. (Box 25)
  - Voice: A Catholic Traditionalist Conservative Newsletter Journal (Canandaigua, NY), v. 1-5 no. 4, 1967-March 6, 1971, 1. (Box 26)
  - Voice: Magazine for Christian Laymen (Chicago, IL: Independent Fundamental Churches of America), v. 45 no. 3-12, March-Dec. 1966; v. 46, 1967; v. 47 no. 1-11, Jan.-Nov. 1968; v. 48, 1969; v. 49 no. 1-2, Jan.-Feb. 1970, 2.
  - Voice of Evangelical Methodism (Newton, KS: Evangelical Methodist Church), v. 14-16, Feb. 1966-Jan. 1969; v. 17 no. 1, Feb. 1969; v. 18 no. 2-12, March 1969-April 1970; v. 19 no. 1-8, May 1970-Feb. 1971, 3.
  - Voice of Freedom (Nashville, TN: Freedom House), v. 14 no. 12, Dec. 1966; v. 16 no. 7-12, July-Dec. 1968; v. 17, 1969; v. 18 no. 1-11, Jan.-Nov. 1970, 4.
  - Voice of Healing (Dallas, TX), v. 19 no. 9, Dec. 1966, 5.
  - Voice of Peace (Independence, MO: The Church of Christ with the Elijah Message), v. 21 no. 8-9, 11-12, April-May, July-Aug. 1966; v. 22 no. 1, 3, Sept., Nov. 1966; v. 23 no. 10-12, June-Aug./Sept. 1968; v. 24 no. 1-9, Oct. 1968-June 1969; v. 25 no. 1, 3, 10, Aug., Oct. 1969, May 1970; v. 26 no. 4-5, Nov.-Dec. 1970, 6.
  - Voice of the Nazarene: A Universal Challenger (Finleyville, PA: The Voice of the Nazarene Association of Independent Churches, Inc.), v. 15 no. 3-12, Aug. 1966-May 1967; v. 16, June 1967-Aug. 1968; v. 17, Sept. 1968-Sept. 1969; v. 18 no. 8, May 1970, 7.
  - Voice of Truth (Knoxville, TN), v. 5 no. 6, 9, July/Aug., Nov./Dec. 1965; v. 6 no. 4, April 1966; v. 7 no. 4-5, 9, April-July/Aug., Nov./Dec. 1967; v. 8, 1968; v. 9, no. 1-3, Jan.-March 1969, 8.
  - Voice of Truth and Freedom (Anaheim, CA: Central Baptist Church), v. 1-6, Nov. 1966-Oct. 1968, 9.
  - Wanderer: A National Catholic Weekly (St. Paul, MN), v. 34 no. 30, 45-53, July 23, Nov.5-Dec. 31, 1964; v. 35, 1965, 10.
  - Wanderer: A National Catholic Weekly (St. Paul, MN), v. 36, 1966; v. 37, 1967 (lacks Jan. 12), 1. (Box 27)
  - Wanderer: A National Catholic Weekly (St. Paul, MN), v. 38, 1968; v. 39, 1969; v. 40 no. 1-5, Jan. 1970, 1. (Box 28)
  - Western Messenger (Yakima, WA: Baptist Church of Yakima), v. 25 no. 11-12, Sept.-Oct. 1966; v. 26 no. 1-2, 6-12, Nov.-Dec. 1966, April-Oct. 1967; v. 27, 1967/1968 (lacks Oct. 1968); v. 28, 1968/1969 (lacks Jan. 1969); v. 29 no. 1-2, Nov.-Dec. 1969, 2.
  - Western Voice: Christ for the Crisis (Englewood, CO; Fort Worth, TX), v. 30 no. 13-43, Aug. 19, 1966-June 29, 1967; v. 31 no. 1-21, 23-24, July 13, 1967-Dec. 14, 1967, Jan. 11-18, 1967; v. 33, Feb. 15-Dec. 26, 1968; v. 34, Jan. 16-May 29, June l9-Oct. 23, Dec. 11-25, 1969; v. 35, Jan. 15-April 9, April 23, May 7, 1970, 3.
  - Wind and Chaff (New York, NY), v. 4 no. 1, Nov. 1966, 4.
  - Witness (Lubbock, TX), v. 8 no. 8, July/Aug. 1968; v. 9 no. 44, April 1969, 5.
  - World Evangelism (Dallas, TX: World Missionary Evangelism), v. 19 no. 10-12, Oct.-Dec. 1977; v. 20 no. 2-6, 8, Feb.-June, Aug. 1978; v. 21 no.1-3, 6, 8, 10-12, Jan.-March, June, Aug., Oct.-Dec. 1979; v. 23 no. 8, 11, Aug., Nov. 1981; v. 24 no. 2, Feb. 1982, 6.
  - World Presbyterian Missions Newsletter (Wilmington, DE), v. 8 no. 6, April 1965; v. 9 no. 4-10, Feb.-Oct. 1966; v. 10-17, 1966/1967-1973/1974; v. 18, 1974/1975 (lacks April 1975); v. 19, 1975/1976 (lacks Jan. Feb., Aug. 1976); v. 20-21, 1976/1977-1977/1978; v. 22, 1978/1979 (lacks Nov. Dec. 1978); v. 23, 1979/1980 (lacks Nov. Dec. 1979; v. 24, 1980/1981; v. 25 no. 3-6, Jan.-April 1982, 7.
- Underground Newspapers, 1967-1976; II.
  This series consists of independently published and distributed newspapers primarily associated with the "social consciousness" youth movements of the late 1960s and early 1970s in the United States and other western nations. They reflect the anti-Vietnam War and pro-civil rights stances of many of these counterculture groups. Newspapers are arranged alphabetically by title.
  - Activist (Buffalo, NY: Buffalo Youth Against War and Fascism), v. 1 no. 3-4, Oct. 5-Dec. 15, 1969, 1. (Box 29)
  - Ann Arbor Argus (Ann Arbor, MI), no. 7-24, 26-29, 33, May 14 1969, July 15, Aug. 5-Sept. 16, Nov. 12, Dec. 17, 1970; no. 37-39, Feb.-April 1971, 2.
  - Asterisk (Omaha, NE), v. 35 no. 2, Nov. 20, 1968, 3.
  - Avatar (Boston, MA), v. 1 no. 13, 19-24, Nov. 24/Dec. 7, 1968, Feb.16/29-April 16/May 9, 1968; v. 2 no. 1-6, May 30-Aug. 29, 1969, 4.
  - Berkeley Tribe (Berkeley, CA), v. 1 no. 1-14, July-Oct. 10/16, 1969, 5.
  - Buddhist 3rd Class Junkmail Oracle (Cleveland, OH), no. 6, Aug. 9, 1967; v. 2 no. 3, Aug./Sept. 1968; Nov. 1968, 6.
  - Catalyst (New Orleans, LA), v. 2 no. 2, Dec. 1969, 7.
  - Chicago Seed (Chicago, IL), v. 1 no. 9-13, Oct. 14/Nov. 3, 1967-1968; v. 2 no. 1-13, 1968; v. 3 no. 1-5, 7-8, 10-13, 1968; v. 4 no. 1, 3-13, 1969/1970; v. 5 no. 1-8, 1970/1971, 8.
  - Connections (Madison, WI), v. 1 no. 4, 6, April, June 1967; v. 2 no. 1-9, Sept. 19, 1967-April 9, 1968, 9.
  - Controversy (Norborne, MO), Jan. 1, June 15, 1976, 10.
  - Berkeley Barb (Berkeley, CA), v. 5 no. 5-26 (103-124) Aug. 4/10, 1967-Dec. 29 Jan. 4, 1968; v. 6 no. 1-26 (125-151) Jan. 5/11-July 5/11, 1968; v. 7 no. 1-8, 13-26 (152-158, 162-176), July 12/18-Aug. 23/29 1968, Sept. 20/26- Dec. 27, 1968/Jan. 2, 1969; v. 8 no. 1- 24 (177-202), Jan. 3/9-June 23/July 3, 1969; v. 9 no. 1-2, 5-29 (203-204, 207-229), July 4/10-July 11, Aug. 1/7, 1969 -Jan. 2/8, 1970; v. 10 no. 1-27 (230 256), Jan. 9/15-July 10/16, 1970; v. 11 no. 1-12 (257-267), July 17/23-Sept: 25/Oct. 1, 1970, 1. (Box 30)
  - Daily Planet (Coconut Grove, FL), v. 1-22, 1969-1970, 1. (Box 31)
  - Notes from the Underground (Dallas, TX), v. 1 no. 10-11, 13-24, 26, May 4-5, 27, 1967-Feb. 3/15, March 3, 1968, 2.
  - Dallas Notes (Dallas, TX), v. 2 no. 1-8, 10, 12 15, 20-21, 23, March 17/31-July 1/15, Aug. 1/15, Sept. 4/17-Oct. 16/Nov. 5, 1968; Feb. 9/March 4-March 5/15, 1969; v. 3 March 19/April 1-Oct. 15/Nov. 4, 1969, 3.
  - Distant Drummer (Philadelphia, PA), no. 12-26, Sept. 1968-March 13/19, 1969; no. 28-97, March 27/April 12-Aug. 6, 1970; no. 100-104, Aug. 20-Sept. 14, 1970, 4.
  - Thursday's Drummer (Philadelphia, PA), no. 106-117, Oct. 2-Dec. 24, 1970; no. 119-131, Jan. 7-April 1, 1971, 5.
  - Dock of the Bay (San Francisco, CA), v. 1 no. 16-17, Nov. 18-25, 1969, 6.
  - East Village Other (New York, NY), v. 2 no. 18-24, Aug. 5/17-Nov. 1/15, 1967; v. 3, Nov. 15/30, 1967-Nov. 1968; v. 4 no. 1-3, 5-20, 22-52, Dec. 6-20, 1968, Jan. 3-April 16, 1969, April 30-Dec. 3, 1969; v. 5 no. 1-24, Dec. 10, 1969-May 12, 1970, 1. (Box 32)
  - Door to Liberation (San Diego, CA), v. 2 no. 1-7, June 4-Aug. 27, 1970, 1. (Box 33)
  - Extra (Providence, RI), v. 1 no. 1-26, Oct. 1/15, 1968-Nov. 4/18, 1969; v. 2 no. 1-8, Dec. 2, 1969-Feb. 3, 1970; v. 4 no. 1-18, May 15, 1969-Jan. 21, 1970, 2.
  - Good News (New Orleans, LA), Jan. 1970, 3.
  - San Francisco Express Times (San Francisco, CA), v. 1 no. 1-49, Jan. 24-Dec. 24, 1968; v. 2 no. 1-12, Jan. 7-March 25, 1969, 4.
  - Good Times (San Francisco, CA), v. 2 no. 13-15, April 2-16, 1969; v. 2 no. 17-20, April 30-May 21, 1969; v. 2 no. 22-49, June 4-Dec. 18, 1969; v. 3 no. 1-25, Jan.-June 19, 1970; v. 3 no. 27-40, July 3-Oct. 9, 1970, 5.
  - Fifth Estate: Detroit's Underground Newspaper (Detroit, MI), v. 2 no. 8, 10-26, July 15, Aug. 15-April 30, 1967; v. 3 no. 1-26, May 1, 1968-May 14, 1969; v. 4 no. 9, Sept. 4/17, 1969, 1. (Box 34)
  - Great Speckled Bird (Atlanta, GA: Atlanta Cooperative News Project), v. 1, no. 1-37, March 15, 1968-March 10, 1969; v. 2 no. 1-39, March 17, 1969-Dec. 8, 1969, 2.
  - Helix (Seattle, WA), v. 4 no. 7-10, 1967/1968; v. 5 no. 1-10, 1968/1969; v. 6 no. 1-10, 1969/1970; v. 7 no. 1-10, 1970/1971; v. 8 no. 1-2, 1971, 1. (Box 35)
  - Heterodoxical Voice (Newark, DE: Newark Free Community, Inc.), no. 5-7, undated, 2.
  - I'm All Right (Pittsburgh, PA), 3 issues, undated, 3.
  - It (London, England), no. 56, May 9-22, 1969, 4.
  - Kaleidoscope (Milwaukee, WI), v. 1-3 no. 6, Oct. 27/Nov. 10, 1967-June 12/25, 1970, 5.
  - Kudzu Project (Jackson, MS: Mississippi Student News), v. 1-2 no. 8, Sept. 18, 1968-Aug. 1970, 6.
  - Liberated Guardian (New York, NY), v. 1 no. 3-8, May 23-Aug. 11, 1970; v. 2 no. 8, Jan. 1972, 7.
  - Madison Kaleidoscope (Madison, WI), v. 1 no. 1, June 23/July 6, 1969; v. 1 no. 5-10, Oct.-Dec., 1970; v. 2-6, 9-19, Jan. 14-March 18, May 5-Sept. 17, 1970, 8.
  - Los Angeles Free Press (Los Angeles, CA), v. 4 no. 32 (no. 160)-v. 5 no. 34 (no. 214), Aug. 11/17, 1967-Aug. 23/29, 1968; v. 5 no. 37 (no. 217) -v. 6 (no. 259), Sept. 13/19, 1968-July 4/11, 1969; v. 6 (no. 261-269), July 18/25, 1969-Sept. 12/18, 1969; v. 6 (no. 271-274), Sept. 16/Oct. 2-Oct. 10/17, 1969; v. 6 (no. 279)- v. 7 no. 13 (no. 327), Nov. 21/28, 1969-Oct. 23/29, 1970, 1. (Box 36)
  - Los Angeles Free Press (Los Angeles, CA), v. 4 no. 32 (no. 160)-v. 5 no. 34 (no. 214), Aug. 11/17, 1967-Aug. 23/29, 1968; v. 5 no. 37 (no. 217) -v. 6 (no. 259), Sept. 13/19, 1968-July 4/11, 1969; v. 6 (no. 261-269), July 18/25, 1969-Sept. 12/18, 1969; v. 6 (no. 271-274), Sept. 16/Oct. 2-Oct. 10/17, 1969; v. 6 (no. 279)- v. 7 no. 13 (no. 327), Nov. 21/28, 1969-Oct. 23/29, 1970 (Box 37)
  - Miami Free Press (Coconut Grove, FL: Jerry Powers), July 18, 1969, 1. (Box 38)
  - Mile High Underground (Denver. CO), v. 1 no. 2-6, April-Fall, 1967, 2.
  - National U (Australia), v. 6 no. 8, July 6, 1970, 3.
  - New Florida Free Press (Jacksonville, FL), no. 6, Nov. 31, 1968, 4.
  - New Orleans News (New Orleans, LA), v. 1 no. 1-4, Jan. 14-Feb. 24, 1970, 5.
  - New York Free Press (New York, NY), v. 1 no. 1, Dec. 28, 1967; v. 1 no. 4-41, Jan. 18-Oct. 7/23, 1968; v. 1 no. 43-48, Oct. 31/Nov. 6-Dec. 12, 1968; v. 1 no. 50, Dec. 19/25, 1968, 6.
  - Newspaper of New Orleans (New Orleans, LA), Dec. 1969; Feb. 23, 1970, 7.
  - Nola Express (New Orleans, LA), no. 17-39, Nov. 15/28, 1968-Sept. 26/Oct. 9, 1969; no. 41-42, Oct. 24/Nov. 6-Nov. 7/20, 1969; no. 44-48, Dec. 5/18, 1969-Feb. 6/19, 1970; no. 50-65, Feb. 6/19-Oct. 2/15, 1970, 8.
  - North Carolinanvil, a weekly newspaper of politics and the arts (Durham, NC), v. 2, no. 59, June 22, 1968; v. 2, no. 79-80, Nov. 16-23, 1968; v. 2, no. 82-v. 3 no. 132, Dec. 7, 1968-Nov. 29, 1969; v. 6, no. 290, Dec. 16, 1972; v. 7, no. 349, Feb. 9, 1974; v. 9, no. 416, May 31, 1975, 9.
  - Octopus (Ottawa, Ont.), v. 2 no. 5-16, Nov. 7, 1968-Dec. 11, 1969; v. 3 no. 1-11, Feb. 16, 1970-Dec. 1, 1970, 10.
  - Old Mole (Boston, MA), v. 1 no. 1-32, Sept. 13, 1968-Feb. 20, 1970, 1. (Box 39)
  - Mole (Boston, MA), v. 2 no. 1, Nov. 20, 1970, 2.
  - Open City: Weekly Review of the Los Angeles Renaissance (Los Angeles, CA), no. 25-92, Oct. 18, 1967-March 1, 1969, 3.
  - Oracle (San Francisco, CA), v. 1 no. 9-10, Aug.-Oct. 1967, 4.
  - Orpheus (Phoenix, AZ), v.1 no. 4, undated, 5.
  - Oz (London, England), April 1969, 6.
  - Paper (East Lansing, MI), v. 2 no. 27, Summer 1967, 7.
  - Partisan (New York, NY: Youth Against War and Fascism), Sept. 15, Nov. 13, 1969, 8.
  - Peninsula Observer (Palo Alto, CA), v. 2 no. 15-29, Jan. 6-June 30, 1969; v. 3 no. 1-6, July 14-Sept. 22, 1969, 9.
  - Pittsburgh Fair Witness (Pittsburgh, PA),v. 1 no. 10, Nov. 1970; v. 2 no. 1, Jan. 1971, 10.
  - Protean Radish: North Carolina's Independent Radical Weekly (Chapel Hill, NC), May 5-Oct. 12, 1969; v. 4 no. 5-25, Oct. 13, 1969-April 14, 1970, 11.
  - Quicksilver Times (Washington, DC), v. 1 no. 13-16, Nov. 13/23-Dec. 19/29, 1969; v. 2 no. 1-9, Jan. 9/19-April 3/13, 1970; v. 2 no. 11-12, May 8/18-May 19/24, 1970; v. 2 no. 14-28, June 9/19-Nov. 24/Dec. 4, 1970, 1. (Box 40)
  - Rag (Austin, TX), v. 1 no. 26, June 5, 1967; v. 2 no. 1, Oct. 10, 1967; v. 2 no. 4-15, Nov. 6, 1967-Feb. 19, 1968; v. 2 no. 17-35, March 4-Aug. 8, 1968; v. 2 no. 37-41, Aug. 22-Oct. 7, 1968; v. 3 no. 1-6, Oct. 14-Nov. 18, 1968; v. 3, no. 12-14, March-May, 1969; v. 3 no. 16-17, June 3-12, 1969; v. 3 no. 19-27, June 26-Aug. 21, 1969; v. 3 no. 29-32, Sept. 15-Oct. 5, 1969; v. 4 no. 1-11, Oct. 13, 1969-Jan. 12, 1970, 2.
  - Rat (New York, NY), v. 1 no.1-2, March 4-March 22/April 4, 1968; v. 1 no. 4-5, April 19/30-May 3/16, 1968; v. 1 no. 10-29, July 1/15-Feb. 14/26, 1969; v. 2 no. 13-16, June 19/July 3-Aug. 12/26, 1969; v. 2 no. 19-20, Sept. 24/Oct. 7-Oct. 8/21, 1969; v. 2 no. 23-28, Dec. 3/16, 1969-Feb. 24/March 9, 1920; v. 3, March 7/21-Aug. 2, 1970, 3.
  - Richmond Chronicle (Richmond, VA), v. 1 no. 3, Sept. 1/15,1969; v. 1 no. 7-10, Nov. 1/15, 1969-Dec. 15/31, 1969; v. 2 no. 1-5, Feb.-June, 1970, 1. (Box 41)
  - Rolling Stone (San Francisco, CA), no. 21, Nov. 9, 1968; no. 25-27, Jan.-Feb. 1969; no. 29-78, March 15, 1969-March 18, 1971, 2.
  - San Diego Door to Liberation (San Diego, CA), v. 1 no. 23-53, March 28-April 10, 1969, 3.
  - Space City News (Houston, TX), v. 1 no. 7, 9-10, Sept. 27, Oct. 25-Nov. 7, 1969, 1. (Box 42)
  - Spectator (Bloomington, IN), v. 5 no. 5-12, Oct. 16-Dec. 11, 1967; v. 6 no. 1-9, Feb. 5-April 21, 1968; v. 7 no. 1-14, Sept. 23, 1968-Jan. 14, 1969; v. 8 no. 1-15, Feb. 4, 1969-May 20, 1969, 2.
  - Spokane Natural (Spokane, WA), v. 1 no. 4, June 9, 1967; v. 1 no. 13, Oct. 14, 1967; v. 2 no. 1, 3-4, Jan. 5/18, 1968, Feb. 2/15-Feb.16/29, 1968, 3.
  - St. Louis Free Press (St. Louis, MO), v. 1 no. 1-16, May 17, 1968-Dec. 13, 1968; v. 2 no. 1-3, March 24-June 9, 1969; v 3 no. 1-3, Sept. 26-Oct. 31, 1969, 4.
  - San Diego Door (La Mesa, CA), v. 1 no. 1-11, Jan. 11/24-May 16/29, 1968, 5.
  - Teaspoon and the Door (San Diego, CA), v. 1 no. 1-22, May 24/31, 1968-March 14/27, 1969, 6.
  - Underground Expose (New York, NY), Jan./Feb. 1969, 7.
  - Virginia Weekly (Charlottesville, VA), v. 4 no. 14, May 1970; v. 5 no. 1-10, Sept. 1970-Aug. 1971; v. 6 no. 1-8, Sept. 1971-June 1972; v. 7 no. 1, Sept. 1972, 8.
  - Washington Free Press (Washington, DC), v. 2 no. 1-52, March 26, 1967-March 31, 1969; v. 3 no. 1-4, 11, April 1- May 31, Nov. 1969, 9.
  - Word of New Orleans (New Orleans, LA), v. 2 no. 1, Jan.2/8, 1969, 10.
- Radical Right Publications, 1915-1978; III.
  This series consists of titles expressing views from the far right of the political spectrum, published by organizations primarily in the United States. They deal with issues such as gun control, white supremacy and anti-communism. Publications are arranged alphabetically by title.
  - ABAS (Newark, NJ), no. 1, 2, 4, Sept., Nov. 1968; Feb. 1969, 1. (Box 43)
  - ACA Index (Washington, DC: Americans for Constitutional Action), 1965-1972, 2.
  - ACU Report (Washington, DC: American Conservative Union), v. 1 no. 1-5, June-Nov. 1966; v. 2 no. 1-3, Jan.-May 1967; v. 3 no. 1-5, Jan.-Oct. 1968; v. 4 no. 2-5, March-Dec. 1969; v. 5 no. 1-2, March-July 1970; Spring/Summer 1974, 3.
  - Academic Reviewer (Bryn Mawr, PA), v. 1 no. 1-2, Feb.-May 1967; v. 2 no. 1-2, Sept. 1967-Feb. 1968, 4.
  - Action Magazine (Hollywood, CA: Sons of Liberty), no. 19-24, 29-30, April-Oct. 1967, Jan.-Feb. 1968; Special issue, undated, 5.
  - Advisor (Three Rivers, MI), 1937-1938; Jan.-Sept., 1939, 6.
  - Advocate ... to plead the cause for decency (Long Beach, CA: California Citizens for Decent Literature), no. 1, Aug. 1963, 7.
  - Agora (Grand Rapids, MI: Constitutional Alliance), v. 1 no. 1-6, 8, Jan. 15-March 31, April 20, 1971, 8.
  - Aim and Fire (Washington, DC: Firearms Lobby of America), no. 3, undated, 9.
  - Birmingham Independent (Birmingham, AL), v. 4, no. 38, Nov. 16/23, 1966; v. 5, no. 6-27, April 19/26-Oct. 25/Nov. 1, 1967, 10.
  - Alabama Independent (Birmingham, AL), v. 5, no. 28-38, 40-48, 51-52, Nov.1/8, 1967-Jan. 24/31, Feb. 7/14-April 3/10, April 24/30-May 1/8, 1968; v. 6, no. 1-52, May 8/15, 1968-July 24, 1969; v. 7, no. 1-52, Aug. 7, 1969-Nov. 1, 1971; v. 8, no. 1-20, Nov. 15, 1971-Sept. 1, 1972, 11.
  - Alert: Calling All Patriots! (Ormond Beach, FL: Defenders of the American Constitution), no. 26, 32, 34-54, Dec. 24, 1965; Aug. 31, 1966; Oct. 24, 1966-Nov. 22, 1968, 12.
  - Alerted Americans (Harrisburg, PA), Spring 1975; Winter-Summer 1976, 13.
  - American Advisor (Sapulpa, OK), v. 4 no. 8, 13, May, Nov. 1961; v. 5 no. 5, May 1962, 14.
  - American Capsule News (Arlington, VA), no. 498, 500-541, Sept., Nov./Dec. 1966-April 1970, 15.
  - American Challenge (Birmingham, AL: Committee of the States), v. 11 no. 2-6, Oct. 15-Dec. 15, 1969; v. 12 no. 1-13, 15, 21-22, Jan.-July 1, Aug. 1, Nov. 15-Dec. 1, 1970; v. 13 no. 1-2, 4, 6, 12-13, Jan. 1-15, Feb. 15, March 15, June 15-July 1, 1971; v. 15 no. 7, April 1, 1973, 16.
  - American Challenger (Los Angeles, CA: American Christian Freedom Society), v. 4 no. 9-12, Sept.-Dec. 1968; v. 5 no. 1-8, Jan.-Oct. 1969; v. 6 no. 1-6, 8/9-12, Jan.-June, Aug./Sept.-Dec. 1970; v. 7 no. 1-8, 10-12, Jan.-Aug., Oct.-Dec. 1971; v. 8-9, 1972-1973; v. 10 no. 3, April 1974, 17.
  - American Commentator (Cedar City, UT), v. 5 no. 15, Oct. 10, 1952, 18.
  - American Destiny (Portland, OR: National Party of America), v. 1 no. 10, June 1966, 19.
  - American Mercury (Oklahoma City, OK), 1958-1962; Jan., Feb., April, July 1963; Jan. 1964; Sept. 1965; 1966-1969; Spring 1970; Summer, Winter 1973; Spring 1974; Spring-Summer 1975, 1. (Box 44)
  - American Mercury Religious Supplement (Oklahoma City, OK), 1 issue, undated, 2.
  - American Mercury Tax Strike Digest (Oklahoma City, OK), Summer 1972, 3.
  - American Opinion (Boston, MA), v. 7 no. 11-12, Nov. Dec. 1964; v. 8 no. 1-11, 1965; v. 9-13, 1966-1970; v. 14, no. 1-9, Jan.-Oct., 1971, 1. (Box 45)
  - American Eagle (Louisville, KY), v. 1 no. 100, undated, 1. (Box 46)
  - American Education Lobby Newsletter (Washington, DC), v. 1 no. 4, Sept. 1968; v. 2 no. 1-5, March-Dec., 1969; v. 3 no. 1-2, Feb.-June 1970, 2.
  - American Flag Committee Newsletter (Philadelphia, PA), no. 64-76, 1963-1969, 3.
  - American Gentile (Los Angeles, CA), v. 1 no. 1, Oct. 23, 1940, 4.